{
    "subject": "resource/Animal_Crossing",
    "predicate": "property/platformOfOrigin",
    "object": "Nintendo 64",
    "human_readable": "Animal Crossing originated on the Nintendo 64 platform.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7455669641494751,
            "question": "On which gaming platform did Animal Crossing first appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6199154257774353,
            "question": "Has Animal Crossing been released on multiple gaming platforms?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5577555894851685,
            "question": "Which company developed the Animal Crossing series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.527850866317749,
            "question": "Describe the gameplay style of Animal Crossing."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48146355152130127,
            "question": "Are there different versions or iterations of Animal Crossing games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.325533390045166,
            "question": "What are some common activities in Animal Crossing games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31948962807655334,
            "question": "What year did the first Animal Crossing game launch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.264259934425354,
            "question": "What makes Animal Crossing a popular video game series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21013952791690826,
            "question": "Is Animal Crossing a single-player or multiplayer game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2003166675567627,
            "question": "What is the name of the popular video game franchise featuring Animal Crossing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Animal Crossing originated on the Nintendo 64 platform.",
            "html": "dbpedia_145_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Animal Crossing a single-player or multiplayer game?",
            "html": "dbpedia_145_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Animal Crossing a popular video game series?",
            "html": "dbpedia_145_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did the first Animal Crossing game launch?",
            "html": "dbpedia_145_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_145_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_145_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_145_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_145_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_145_163.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_145_167.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_145_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_145_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_145_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_145_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Animal Crossing originated on the Nintendo 64 platform.\" Specifically, multiple sources indicate that the original version of Animal Crossing was released in Japan for the Nintendo 64 in 2001 before being ported to the GameCube."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}